PREVIOUSLY ON E.R.:
所以，四个候选人，包括我。
SO, FOUR CANDIDATES
INCLUDING ME.
实际上...
ACTUALLY...
你让它变成了五个。
YOU MAKE IT FIVE.
这个助听器很贵。
THIS HEARING AID IS EXPENSIVE.
我发现保险不报销。
I FOUND OUT INSURANCE
WON'T COVER.
我说过我们分享一切，我是说一切，好吗？
I SAID THAT WE SHARE EVERYTHING
AND I MEANT EVERYTHING, OKAY?
我在人体模型上练习静脉注射。
I PRACTICE MY I.V.s
ON A MANNEQUIN.
很好。但要知道何时寻求帮助。
GOOD. BUT KNOW WHEN
TO ASK FOR HELP.
我希望你为新的儿科急诊室主治医生：我，干杯。
I WANT YOU TO TOAST THE NEW
PEDES E.R. ATTENDING: ME.
我听说过外国医生
I HAVE HEARD OF
FOREIGN DOCTORS
他们愿意从实习生做起。
WHO WERE WILLING TO
START OVER AS INTERNS.
如果他们截肢，我一定能活吗？
IF THEY AMPUTATE,
IS IT CERTAIN I'LL LIVE?
看起来它停在两个半街区外。
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S STOPPED
LIKE TWO-AND-A-HALF BLOCKS.
也许我们应该从这里步行。
MAYBE WE SHOULD
HOOF IT FROM HERE.
我不知道。
I DON'T KNOW.
你不是应该制定政策吗？
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE SETTING POLICY?
我来这里是为了搭车。
I'M HERE FOR
THE RIDE-ALONG.
我讨厌单行道。
I HATE ONE-WAY STREETS.
这不算什么。
THIS IS NOTHING.
我曾经在Metallica演唱会中间
I ONCE RESPONDED
TO A CELL PHONE CALL
接听过手机。
FROM THE MIDDLE OF
A METALLICA CONCERT.
试试让一个过敏的甩头客
TRY GETTING
AN ANAPHYLACTIC HEAD BANGER
通过10000个疯子。
PAST 10,000 MANIACS.
那家伙吸了点迷幻剂，开始数乌鸦。
GUY DROPPED SOME ACID
STARTED HIM COUNTING CROWS.
我每天都经历这些。
I LIVE WITH THIS
EVERY DAY.
你对工作人员分配有什么影响力吗？
YOU GOT ANY PULL
WITH CREW ASSIGNMENTS?
嘿，嘿，嘿。
HEY, HEY, HEY.
你能帮我们分配到熊队比赛
CAN YOU GET US ASSIGNED
TO THE MED TEAM
的医疗队吗？
AT THE BEARS GAME?
我不负责排班。
I DON'T DO THE
SCHEDULING.
太糟糕了；你差点成为我最好的新朋友。
TOO BAD; YOU WERE ALMOST
MY NEW BEST FRIEND.
嘿，嘿，嘿！让开！
HEY, HEY, HEY!
MAKE WAY!
嘿！急救人员来了！
HEY! PARAMEDICS
COMING THROUGH!
嘿，嘿！退后！
HEY, HEY!
STAND BACK!
给我们点空间。给我们点空间。
GIVE US SOME ROOM.
看起来像一个…哇，哇，天哪！
LOOKS LIKE A SINGLE...
WHOA, WHOA, GEEZ!
是Cujo！
IT'S CUJO!
他正在保护他的主人。
HE'S PROTECTING
HIS OWNER.
好的，你开门。
OKAY, YOU OPEN
THE DOOR.
先生，你能听到我吗？
SIR, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
他呼吸了吗？
IS HE BREATHING?
他的胸部正在动。
HIS CHEST
IS MOVING.
有什么主意吗？
GOT ANY IDEAS?
你问我？
YOU'RE ASKING ME?
57号单元呼叫O.C.D.，完毕。
UNIT 57 TO O.C.D., OVER.
一点点狗狗安定剂？
A LITTLE PUPPY VALIUM?
我们需要动物控制到第四街和兰花街。
WE NEED ANIMAL CONTROL
AT FOURTH AND ORCHID.
狗挡住了M.V.A.受害者的通道，完毕。
DOG BARRING ACCESS
TO AN M.V.A. VICTIM, OVER.
那会花太长时间的。看这个。
IT'LL TAKE TOO LONG.
LOOK AT THIS.
他说得对。我们必须进去。
HE'S RIGHT. WE'VE
GOT TO GET IN THERE.
你有什么建议？
WHAT DO
YOU SUGGEST?
我车上有一把枪。
I GOT A GUN IN THE RIG.
我来拖住他。
I'LL KEEP HIM BUSY.
你在开玩笑吧？
YOU'RE
KIDDING, RIGHT?
不，我们现在必须评估他。
NO, WE'VE GOT TO ASSESS HIM NOW.
你是老板。
YOU'RE THE BOSS.
嘿，小家伙。
HEY, BOY.
嘿，嘿，嘿，准备好了吗？一…二…
HEY, HEY, HEY, READY?
ONE... TWO...
三！嘿！
THREE! HEY!
有脉搏。
GOT A PULSE.
呼吸音良好。拿一个担架。
GOOD BREATH SOUNDS.
GET A BACKBOARD.
你还好吗？是啊，我就是放不开。
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I JUST CAN'T LET GO.
HALEH？
HALEH?
一剂增强剂马上就好。
ONE BOOSTER
COMING RIGHT UP.
没关系。我不要。
THAT'S OKAY. I'LL PASS.
可能会更糟。你可能会得狂犬病。
IT COULD BE WORSE.
YOU COULD HAVE RABIES.
我不会排除这种可能性。
I WOULDN'T RULE IT OUT.
你觉得我们会注意到区别吗？
THINK WE'D NOTICE
A DIFFERENCE?
（咯咯笑）
( chuckling )
那么，今天有多少次面试？
SO, HOW MANY
INTERVIEWS TODAY?
两次。
TWO. YOU AND ONE OTHER.
你和另外一个人。
I'M STILL INTERESTED
我仍然感兴趣
BUT I DECIDED NOT
TO PUSH SO HARD.
但我决定不再那么努力了。
I MEAN, IF I GET IT
我的意思是，如果我得到了
YOU KNOW, I GET IT.
你知道，我就得到了。
GOOD IDEA.
好主意。
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
你什么意思？
IT'S JUST NOT A GOOD IDEA
TO GET WORKED UP
只是不值得为这些事情操心。
OVER THESE THINGS.
你发生什么事了？
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
呃，说来话长。
UGH, LONG STORY.
瑞秋的睡衣派对？
RACHEL'S SLEEPOVER?
猜得好。
GOOD GUESS.
谢谢，凯利。
THANKS, KERRY.
这里发生了什么？
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
昨晚涂鸦者疯了。
TAGGERS WENT CRAZY
LAST NIGHT.
是吗？
YEAH?
你上班了？
YOU'RE ON?
不，我正在为明天做准备。
NO, I'M GETTING SET UP
FOR TOMORROW.
颜色协调的图表？
COLOR-COORDINATED
CHARTS?
嗯，谁说道格·罗斯不整理的？
WELL, WHOEVER SAID
DOUG ROSS ISN'T ORGANIZED?
（咯咯笑）：放松点。
( chuckling ):
TAKE IT EASY.
嘿，嗯，马克？
HEY, UM, MARK?
主治医生不是应该为护士之夜买单吗？
DON'T ATTENDINGS PAY
FOR NURSES NIGHT?
是啊，现在道格可以贡献了。
YEAH, NOW DOUG
CAN CONTRIBUTE.
那是急诊室，我是儿科急诊室。
THAT'S THE E.R.
I'M THE PEDES E.R.
是啊，嗯，儿科需要护士，对吧？
YEAH, WELL, PEDES
NEEDS NURSES, RIGHT?
所以我要向你收费。
SO I'M BILLING YOU.
嘿，听着。
HEY, GET THIS.
19岁，第三次怀孕
19-YEAR-OLD,
THIRD PREGNANCY
她说她不知道怎么用避孕套。
SAYS SHE DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO USE A CONDOM.
那么，你教她了吗？
SO, DID YOU TEACH HER?
哦，不，我们早就过了那个阶段了。
OH, NO, WE'RE
WAY PAST THAT.
我正在说服她接受一个新的计划。
I'M TALKING HER INTO
A NEWER PLAN.
你确定吗？
ARE YOU SURE?
如果可以的话，我真想给她结扎。
I'D TIE HER TUBES
MYSELF, IF I COULD.
我不知道，吊桥已经升起来了
I DON'T KNOW,
THE DRAWBRIDGE IS UP
你不能攻城。
YOU CAN'T STORM THE CASTLE.
打扰一下？
EXCUSE ME?
试试子宫帽。它们管用。
TRY A DIAPHRAGM.
THEY WORK.
我可不敢太肯定。我迟了三天。
I WOULDN'T BE TOO SURE.
I'M THREE DAYS LATE.
嗯哼。
MM-HMM.
什么？什么？
WHAT? WHAT?
这些刚从楼上送来。
THESE JUST CAME FROM UPSTAIRS.
主任的推荐信。
LETTERS OF REC FOR CHIEF.
谢谢你。
THANK YOU.
抬起你的袖子。
LIFT YOUR SLEEVE.
上次有人被狗咬得破伤风是什么时候？
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME SOMEONE
GOT TETANUS FROM A DOG BITE?
别像个孩子似的。
DON'T BE A BABY.
这西装真好看，韦弗医生。谢谢你。
NICE SUIT,
DR. WEAVER.
THANK YOU.
我不知道你读《时尚》。
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU READ COSMO.
打扰一下？哎哟！
EXCUSE ME?
OW!
关于权力套装的文章？
THE ARTICLE ON
THE POWER SUIT?
哦，呃，我猜我错过了那个。
OH, UH, I GUESS
I MISSED THAT ONE.
哦，你确定吗？
OH, ARE YOU SURE?
因为，我的意思是，你连配饰都完美了。
'CAUSE, I MEAN, YOU NAILED
IT DOWN TO THE ACCESSORIES.
你工作多久了？
SO HOW LONG
HAVE YOU BEEN ON?
哦，刚开始。
OH, JUST NOW.
是吗？你的住院医生是谁？
YEAH? WHO'S YOUR RESIDENT?
哦，嗯，我想我一分钟后就会知道了。
OH, WELL I SUPPOSE I'LL
FIND OUT IN A MINUTE.
为什么？你为我竞争过吗？
WHY? DID YOU VIE FOR ME?
（笑）
( laughs )
你太难对付了。
YOU'RE TOO MUCH
FOR ME TO HANDLE.
（笑）
( laughs )
希望我得到的任何人都有同感。
HOPEFULLY, WHOEVER I
GET FEELS THE SAME WAY.
不，我怀疑我更多的是作为顾问
NO, I SUSPECT I'LL
BE SIDELINED AS
A CONSULTANT
被边缘化。
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
是啊。
YEAH.
嘿，帮我个忙。
HEY, DO ME A FAVOR.
从他包里拿出他的助听器。
REACH IN HIS BAG
AND HAND ME HIS
HEARING AID.
在黑色的盒子里，在最上面。
IT'S IN THE BLACK CASE,
ON TOP.
他戴这个有麻烦吗？
IS HE HAVING TROUBLE
WITH THESE?
没有。
NO.
那为什么你现在戴上它们？
SO WHY ARE YOU
PUTTING THEM ON NOW?
我迟到了。
I WAS RUNNING LATE.
彼得，你没告诉所有人吗？
PETER, HAVE YOU NOT
TOLD EVERYONE?
告诉谁？
TOLD WHO?
听着，伊丽莎白，我没时间
LOOK, ELIZABETH,
I DON'T HAVE TIME
回答一堆重复的问题和…和同情。
FOR A WHOLE BUNCH OF
REPETITIVE QUESTIONS
AND... AND SYMPATHY.
你确定就是这样吗？
YOU SURE THAT'S IT?
我儿子聋了。我知道，好吗？
MY SON IS DEAF.
I KNOW THAT, OKAY?
好的。好的。
OKAY. OKAY.
祝我好运。
WELL, WISH ME LUCK.
杰夫·惠彻，38岁的魔术师，吸入了闪光粉。
JEFF WHITCHER,
38-YEAR-OLD MAGICIAN,
INHALED FLASH POWDER.
发生什么事了？
WHAT HAPPENED?
活板门没开。
TRAP DOOR DIDN'T OPEN.
比那更复杂一点。
A LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED
THAN THAT.
气短和呼吸急促。
SHORT OF BREATH
AND TACHYPNEIC.
呃，呼吸频率是28。
UH, RESPIRATORY
RATE IS 28.
没有呼吸系统疾病史
NO PREVIOUS HISTORY
OF RESPIRATORY ILLNESS
或吸入有毒物质。
OR INHALATION OF
TOXIC SUBSTANCES.
闪光粉里有什么？
WHAT'S IN FLASH POWDER?
抱歉。商业机密。
SORRY. TRADE SECRET.
石松粉和硝酸钾。
LYCOPODIUM WRAPPED WITH
POTASSIUM NITRATE.
我在网上查了一下。
I LOOKED IT UP
ON THE INTERNET.
血氧饱和度临界值91。
PULSE OX IS
BORDERLINE 91.
无发绀。
NO CYANOSIS.
你抽烟吗？
YOU A SMOKER?
偶尔。
OCCASIONAL.
是啊。职业病。
YEAH. OCCUPATIONAL HAZARD.
你不能在这里抽烟。
YOU CAN'T SMOKE
THAT HERE.
没打算。
WASN'T PLANNING TO.
（咳嗽）
( coughing )
你想怎么办？
WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO?
抽血气并检查血氧分压。
GET A BLOOD GAS
AND CHECK A pO2.
看来你要学习一个新的程序了。
LOOKS LIKE YOU GET
TO LEARN A NEW PROCEDURE.
我正好这里有一个血气套件。
I JUST HAPPEN TO
HAVE A BLOOD GAS
KIT RIGHT HERE.
嘿，干得不错，医生。
HEY, PRETTY GOOD, DOC.
商业机密。
TRADE SECRET.
莉莉，能给我们拿杯冰块吗？
LILY, CAN YOU GET US
A CUP OF ICE?
好的。
SURE.
我们没有手套了。我马上回来。
WE'RE OUT OF GLOVES.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
摸摸你的口袋。
TRY YOUR POCKET.
嘿，你是怎么做到的？他抓着你的胳膊。
HEY, HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
HE'S GOT YOUR ARM.
这不是他们看到的
IT'S NOT WHAT THEY SEE
而是他们以为他们看到的。
IT'S WHAT THEY THINK
THEY SEE.
但你甚至没动。
BUT YOU DIDN'T
EVEN MOVE.
露西？是的。
LUCY?
YES.
血气。
A BLOOD GAS.
这个你看着，下一个你来做。
THIS ONE YOU WATCH,
NEXT ONE YOU DO.
别慌，道格。就几天。
DON'T PANIC, DOUG.
IT'S JUST A COUPLE OF DAYS.
亲爱的，你说三天。
HONEY, YOU SAID
THREE DAYS.
你说三天。
YOU SAID THREE.
两天，三天，随便。
TWO, THREE, WHATEVER.
你告诉我你像瑞士手表一样准时。
YOU TOLD ME YOU
WERE REGULAR AS
A SWISS WATCH.
是啊，我准时，不是机器。
YEAH, I'M REGULAR,
NOT A MACHINE.
你要做怀孕测试吗，还是…？
ARE YOU GOING TO DO
A PREGNANCY TEST, OR...?
你真的很紧张这个。
YOU'RE REALLY
SWEATING THIS.
有点是吧？
AREN'T YOU, A LITTLE?
我没怀孕。我感觉不到。
I'M NOT PREGNANT.
I DON'T FEEL IT.
你以前怀孕过吗？
HAVE YOU BEEN
PREGNANT BEFORE?
我不该说出来的。
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
SAID ANYTHING.
（女人说西班牙语）
( woman speaking Spanish )
呃，他昏迷了多久…嗯…
UH, CUANTO TIEMPO TIENE
FAINTED... UM...
怎么了？发生什么事了？
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT HAPPENED?
晕厥。第四次发作。
SYNCOPE.
FOURTH EPISODE.
癫痫？我不这么认为。
SEIZURE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
我以为你今天不当班。
I THOUGHT YOU
WEREN'T ON TODAY.
我不是。我们用儿科病房，不用等。
I'M NOT. LET'S USE THE
PEDES ROOM, NO WAITING.
我们走吧…嘿，这是什么？
HERE WE GO...
HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
可能是卡特的。他们积压了。
COULD BE CARTER'S.
THEY WERE BACKED UP.
卡特！这是你的尸体吗？
CARTER! IS THIS
YOUR BODY IN HERE?
是啊，抱歉。
YEAH, SORRY.
运输慢死了。你需要房间吗？
TRANSPORT'S TAKING FOREVER.
YOU NEED THE ROOM?
是的，我需要房间。
YEAH, I NEED
THE ROOM.
帮我一把？
GIVE ME A HAND?
我以为儿科急诊室明天才开门呢。
I DIDN'T THINK THE PEDES E.R.
WAS OPEN UNTIL TOMORROW.
别把你的尸体留在这里。
DON'T LEAVE YOUR
STIFFS IN HERE.
露西，把他送到太平间。
LUCY, TAKE HIM TO THE MORGUE.
我们已经等了三个小时的转运了。
WE'VE BEEN WAITING ON
A TRANSFER FOR THREE HOURS.
这是阿尔伯特王子吗？谁？
IS THIS THE
PRINCE ALBERT?
WHO?
他的丁丁穿孔了。
HIS DING DONG'S PIERCED.
他应该戴一颗钻石。在他的阴茎里？
HE'S SUPPOSED TO
HAVE A DIAMOND.
IN HIS PENIS?
黑尔说导尿管很难放进去。
HALEH SAYS IT WAS TRICKY
GETTING IN THE FOLEY.
想看看吗？我见过一个。
WANT TO TAKE A PEEK?
I'VE SEEN ONE.
我敢打赌。嘿，小心点。
I BET.
HEY, WATCH IT.
我想你今天走运了。
I GUESS IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY.
看来我是你的实习生。
IT SEEMS I'M
YOUR INTERN.
我知道。你错过了查房。
I KNOW. YOU MISSED ROUNDS.
哦，第一天嘛。
OH, IT'S THE FIRST DAY.
我不知道这会怎么运作。
I WASN'T SURE HOW
THIS WAS GOING TO WORK.
你需要早上五点准时到这里。
YOU NEED TO BE HERE
AT 5:00 A.M. SHARP.
我希望你不要期望任何特殊待遇。
I HOPE YOU DON'T EXPECT
ANY SPECIAL TREATMENT.
听着，我不知道你被告知了什么
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN TOLD
但这更多的是一种形式。
BUT THIS IS MORE OF A FORMALITY
THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
也许对你来说是这样，但你是我唯一的实习生。
MAYBE FOR YOU, BUT
YOU'RE THE ONLY
INTERN I HAVE.
我需要你在六点前完成预查房。
I NEED YOU TO FINISH
PRE-ROUNDING BEFORE 6:00.
我需要所有的生命体征。
I NEED ALL THE VITALS.
最高体温、精神状态、出入量。
T-MAX, MENTAL STATUS,
Is AND Os.
查房后，检查实验室结果并查阅所有X光片。
AFTER ROUNDS, CHECK THE LABS
AND RUN DOWN ALL X RAYS.
自己检查X光片。
GO OVER THE X RAYS YOURSELF.
不要相信放射科医生。
DON'T TRUST THE RADIOLOGIST.
根据需要补充电解质。
BUFF THE ELECTROLYTES
AS NEEDED.
你接所有的楼层电话。
YOU TAKE ALL FLOOR CALLS.
如果我们那天有门诊，你做病史和体格检查
IF WE HAVE CLINIC THAT
DAY, YOU DO H&Ps
当然，还有所有术前医嘱：
AND OF COURSE,
ALL PRE-OP ORDERS:
全血细胞计数、电解质、尿液分析、心电图、凝血酶原时间。
C.B.C., LYTES, U.A.,
E.K.G., P.T.
我知道如何对病人进行术前准备，谢谢。
I DO KNOW HOW TO PRE-OP
A PATIENT, THANK YOU.
那很好，因为如果手术取消了
WELL, GOOD, BECAUSE IF
SURGERY'S CANCELED
因为你漏掉了检查，那是你的责任。
BECAUSE YOU MISS A LAB,
IT'S YOUR ASS.
我们从安德森先生开始。
WE'LL START WITH
MR. ANDERSON.
我降低了他的氧气。
I REDUCED HIS O2.
30分钟后重新抽血气。
REDRAW AN A.B.G.
IN 30 MINUTES.
每小时监测尿量。
MONITOR URINE OUTPUT
Q ONE HOUR.
推进3号和5号床的引流管。
ADVANCE DRAINS
ON BEDS THREE AND FIVE.
1号、2号和6号需要湿对干换药。
ONE, TWO AND SIX NEED
WET-TO-DRY DRESSING CHANGES.
（笑）：你是认真的。
( laughing ):
YOU'RE SERIOUS.
就是这样。
THIS IS HOW IT WORKS.
作为三年级，我忙着手术。
AS THIRD YEAR,
I'M BUSY OPERATING.
这些东西不是我的工作
THIS STUFF IS
NOT MY JOB
但琐事必须由…
BUT THE SCUT
HAS TO BE DONE...
一个实习生来完成。
BY AN INTERN.
我今天有三个病例。
I HAVE THREE CASES TODAY.
如果你完成了，你可以参加一个。
IF YOU FINISH,
YOU CAN SCRUB IN FOR ONE.
哦，这是给你的。
OH, AND THIS IS FOR YOU.
实习生穿短外套。
INTERNS WEAR SHORT COATS.
老头：等等电梯！
Old Man:
HOLD THE ELEVATOR!
等等！
HOLD IT!
你没事吧？
YOU ALL RIGHT?
我说等等电梯。
I SAID HOLD THE ELEVATOR.
警察：他穿什么了？
Policeman:
WHAT WAS HE WEARING?
我不知道。
I DON'T KNOW.
我们到了哪里？
WHERE ARE WE?
四肢多处防御性刺伤。
MULTIPLE DEFENSIVE STAB WOUNDS
TO THE EXTREMITIES.
前臂深处一处，胸部一处。
A DEEP ONE TO THE FOREARM
AND ONE TO THE CHEST.
血压120/75。血氧饱和度99。
B.P.'s 120/75. PULSE OX 99.
那家伙有朋友和他在一起吗？
DID THE GUY HAVE
FRIENDS WITH HIM?
双肺清晰。
BOTH LUNGS
ARE CLEAR.
右桡动脉和尺动脉搏动4+。
FOUR PLUS RIGHT RADIAL
AND ULNAR PULSES.
你叫什么名字？
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
波。
BO.
我们会照顾你的。
WE'RE GOING TO
TAKE CARE OF YOU.
是啊，你很幸运。
YEAH, YOU'RE VERY LUCKY.
胸部伤口是表面的。
THE CHEST WOUND IS
SUPERFICIAL.
我希望你用手做这个。
I WANT YOU TO DO THIS
WITH YOUR HAND.
波，有车吗？你看到车了吗？
HOW ABOUT A CAR, BO?
DID YOU SEE A CAR?
张开手指，别让我合拢。
SPREAD YOUR FINGERS
AND DON'T LET ME
CLOSE THEM.
我厌倦了这个游戏。
I'M TIRED OF THIS GAME.
告诉我那是谁。
JUST TELL ME
WHO IT WAS.
他必须在这里吗？
DOES HE HAVE TO BE HERE?
你为什么不在外面等？
WHY DON'T YOU
WAIT OUTSIDE?
那是大白天。
IT WAS BROAD DAYLIGHT.
你什么也没看见吗？
YOU DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING?
你知道吗？在外面等。
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WAIT OUTSIDE.
好的，我们把他翻过来。
OKAY, LET'S ROLL HIM.
他会出去自己解决这件事。
HE'S GOING TO GO OUT
AND TRY AND SETTLE
THIS ON HIS OWN.
现在我们必须治疗他。
RIGHT NOW WE HAVE
TO TREAT HIM.
你知道吗？算了。
YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET IT.
随你便。
HAVE IT YOUR WAY.
你可以按那个暂停按钮的。
YOU COULD HAVE PRESSED
THAT HOLD BUTTON.
该死，这些电梯太慢了。
DAMN, THESE
ELEVATORS ARE SLOW.
我要赶午餐高峰
I'M GOING TO CATCH
THAT LUNCH TRAFFIC
我知道。
I KNOW IT.
你开车吗？
YOU DRIVE?
经常。（寻呼机响）
A LOT.
( pager beeping )
我儿子以前也有一个。
MY SON USED TO HAVE
ONE OF THOSE.
让他心脏病发作了。
GAVE HIM A HEART ATTACK.
全是压力。
NOTHING BUT STRESS.
来吧。来吧。
COME ON. COME ON.
但我看到的那部分看起来很良性。
BUT THE PART I SAW
LOOKED PRETTY BENIGN.
是我的错。抱歉。
IT WAS MY FAULT. SORRY.
嗯，你确实是。谢谢。
WELL, YOU DID.
THANKS.
有问题吗？
PROBLEM?
你知道《罗密欧与朱丽叶》是PG-13级的吗？
DID YOU KNOW THAT ROMEO
AND JULIET IS RATED PG-13?
我不知道，没有。
I WASN'T AWARE OF IT, NO.
嗯，它就是，我在瑞秋的睡衣派对上放了它
WELL, IT IS, AND I SHOWED IT
AT RACHEL'S SLUMBER PARTY
现在所有的妈妈都给我打电话。
AND NOW ALL THE MOTHERS
ARE CALLING ME.
哦，是啊。
OH, YEAH.
伊丽莎白？
ELIZABETH?
伊丽莎白！
ELIZABETH!
你能来看看一个无脉的脚吗？
CAN YOU COME TAKE A LOOK
AT A PULSELESS FOOT?
我等外科会诊等了40分钟。
I'VE BEEN WAITING 40 MINUTES
FOR A SURGICAL CONSULT.
通常我会，但从今天起我只是个实习生。
NORMALLY I WOULD,
BUT AS OF TODAY
I'M ONLY AN INTERN.
我听说过。我简直不敢相信。
I HEARD ABOUT THAT.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
我自己也不想相信。
I DON'T WANT
TO BELIEVE IT MYSELF.
我已经有五个入院病人了。
I ALREADY HAVE
FIVE ADMISSIONS.
实验室出结果的时间太慢了
LAB TURNAROUND TIME
IS PATHETIC
放射科已经丢了我三张片子。
AND RADIOLOGY HAVE ALREADY LOST
THREE OF MY FILMS.
同时，戴尔让我为你的尤因肉瘤截肢
MEANWHILE, DALE HAS ME SITTING
FOR A BLEEDING TIME
做凝血时间
ON YOUR EWING
SARCOMA AMPUTATION
这完全是浪费时间。
WHICH IS A COMPLETE
WASTE OF TIME.
你说的是达娜·埃利斯吗？
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT DANA ELLIS?
是的。她没有凝血问题。
YES. SHE DOESN'T HAVE
A CLOTTING PROBLEM.
是今天吗？
IS THAT TODAY?
手术定在下午4点。
SURGERY'S SCHEDULED
FOR 4:00 P.M.
五分钟。54岁男性
FIVE MINUTES.
54-YEAR-OLD MALE
外周血管疾病，静息时有导管疼痛。
PERIPHERAL VASCULAR DISEASE,
CATH PAIN AT REST.
我怀疑是动脉血栓。
I'M THINKING
ARTERIAL THROMBOSIS.
你做过多普勒超声吗？
DID YOU GET
A DOPPLER PULSE?
是的。达西先生，这是科迪医生，我们的外科住院医生。
YEAH. MR. DARCY,
THIS IS DR. CORDAY
OUR SURGICAL RESIDENT.
这会让我停工多久？
HOW LONG WILL THIS KEEP ME
OUT OF COMMISSION?
我下周要编排一个音乐视频。
I'M SUPPOSED TO CHOREOGRAPH
A MUSIC VIDEO NEXT WEEK.
嗯，让我先检查一下你
WELL, LET ME EXAMINE
YOU FIRST
我会有更清楚的了解。
AND I'LL HAVE
A CLEARER IDEA.
你抽烟吗？
ARE YOU A SMOKER?
是的，但这和我的腿有什么关系？
YES, BUT WHAT HAS THAT
GOT TO DO WITH MY LEG?
这是血管科会诊吗？
THIS THE VASCULAR CONSULT?
是啊。
YEAH. I ASKED
DR. CORDAY
TO EXAMINE.
我让科迪医生检查。
I'LL TAKE OVER.
DID YOU GET THE LABS
我来接手。你拿到穿孔憩室的化验结果了吗？
ON THE PERFED DIVERTICULUM?
还没准备好。
NOT READY YET.
最好下去盯着他们。
BETTER GO DOWN THERE
AND SIT ON THEM.
你知道罗马诺——必须准时开始。
YOU KNOW ROMANO--
GOT TO START ON TIME.
当然。
OF COURSE.
来吧。
COME ON.
露西？
LUCY?
什么？
WHAT?
有什么不对劲吗？没有。
IS SOMETHING
WRONG?
NOPE.
你能帮我处理这个眩晕症患者吗？
CAN YOU WORK UP THIS GUY
WITH VERTIGO FOR ME?
你知道怎么检查眼震和小脑功能吗？
YOU KNOW HOW TO CHECK
FOR NYSTAGMUS AND
CEREBELLAR FUNCTION?
是啊？好吧。
YEAH? ALL RIGHT.
完了来找我。
COME FIND ME
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
我们讨论鉴别诊断。
WE'LL DISCUSS
THE DIFFERENTIAL.
明白了。
GOT IT.
太平间的总机号码是多少？
WHAT'S THE EXTENSION
FOR THE MORGUE?
5001。
5001.
看到这个人了吗？
SEE THIS GUY?
他正在找卡特医生。
HE'S LOOKING
FOR DR. CARTER.
我能帮你吗？
CAN I HELP YOU?
是的。我哥哥昨晚去世了。
YEAH. MY BROTHER
DIED LAST NIGHT.
他们把他的贵重物品给了我
THEY GAVE ME
HIS VALUABLES
但少了一些东西。
BUT THERE'S
SOMETHING MISSING.
我需要把…
I NEED TO GET A...
嗯，一些珠宝从他身上取下来。
WELL, SOME JEWELRY
OFF HIS BODY.
哦，对了。对了。
OH, RIGHT. RIGHT.
哦，你哥哥在太平间。
OH, YOUR BROTHER'S
DOWN IN THE MORGUE.
姓诺顿吗？是的，是的。
LAST NAME NAUGHTON?
YES, YES.
肯定在太平间。
DEFINITELY
DOWN IN THE MORGUE.
哦…你能告诉我怎么去吗？
OH... CAN YOU TELL ME
HOW TO GET THERE?
是啊。不。
YEAH. NO.
呃，他们不让家属下去。
UH, THEY DON'T ALLOW FAMILY
DOWN THERE.
那，呃…
IT'S, UH...
他们让你等着。
THEY MAKE YOU WAIT.
那会花很长时间的。
IT TAKES FOREVER.
很冷。
IT'S CHILLY.
你知道我要做什么吗？
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO?
我要下去把它拿回来。
I'M GOING TO GO DOWN THERE
AND I'M GOING TO GET IT.
你哥哥。把他哥哥
YOUR BROTHER.
GET YOUR BROTHER
带到这里来给你。
AND BRING HIM
BACK UP HERE FOR YOU.
太好了。
GREAT.
那太好了。谢谢你。
THAT'D BE GREAT.
THANK YOU.
不客气。
DON'T MENTION IT.
嘿。
HEY.
你在这里做什么？
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
只是来看看你。
JUST CAME IN TO
CHECK IN ON YOU.
你感觉怎么样？
HOW YOU FEELING?
嗯，他们要截掉我的腿。
WELL, THEY'RE
CHOPPING MY LEG OFF.
是啊。
YEAH.
你的决定？
YOUR DECISION?
你可以这么说。
YOU COULD
CALL IT THAT.
如果没有你，我根本没有发言权。
I WOULDN'T HAVE HAD A SAY
AT ALL IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU.
得跟着概率走，对吧？
GOT TO GO
WITH THE ODDS, RIGHT?
你害怕吗？
YOU SCARED?
我以为，“好吧，我习惯了。”
I THOUGHT, "OKAY, I'LL JUST
GET USED TO IT."
但是…
BUT...
你疼吗？
YOU IN PAIN?
有点。
A LITTLE.
是啊。好的，我去和他们谈谈，增加你的剂量。
YEAH. OKAY, I'LL TALK TO THEM
AND INCREASE YOUR DOSAGE.
没关系。我有点…
THAT'S OKAY.
I SORT OF...
喜欢感受它。
LIKE TO FEEL IT.
几个小时后就会消失。
IT'LL BE GONE IN A FEW HOURS.
（门开）
( door opens )
嗨，埃利斯先生。
HI, MR. ELLIS.
这里发生了什么事？
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
只是来看看达娜。
JUST CAME IN
TO CHECK IN ON DANA.
她正在被照顾，谢谢。
SHE'S BEING TAKEN CARE OF,
THANK YOU.
嗯哼。听着，我想和你谈谈
MM-HMM. LISTEN,
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
关于她的疼痛管理。
ABOUT HER PAIN MANAGEMENT.
达娜几个小时后就要手术了。
DANA'S HAVING SURGERY
IN A FEW HOURS.
如果你不介意
IF YOU DON'T MIND
罗马诺医生会处理这里的一切。
DR. ROMANO IS GOING TO HANDLE
EVERYTHING FROM HERE.
好的。
OKAY.
对不起。
EXCUSE ME.
你是负责运输的吗？
ARE YOU IN CHARGE
OF TRANSPORT?
取决于谁问。
DEPENDS WHO'S ASKING.
我知道这听起来很奇怪
I KNOW THIS IS GOING
TO SOUND REALLY WEIRD
但我只是想知道你是否碰巧找到了一具尸体。
BUT I WAS JUST WONDERING IF YOU,
BY ANY CHANCE, FOUND A BODY.
（电话响）
( phone rings )
运输。
TRANSPORT.
是啊，哪层？
YEAH, WHAT FLOOR?
好的。
OKAY.
我不知道。半小时。
I DON'T KNOW. HALF HOUR.
该死！
DAMN!
你想要什么？
WHAT DID YOU WANT?
我丢了一具尸体。
I LOST A BODY.
对。你试图自己搬动它吗？
RIGHT. DID YOU TRY
TO MOVE IT YOURSELF?
嗯，是啊，你们太慢了。
WELL, YEAH, YOU GUYS
WERE TAKING TOO LONG.
我该怎么办？
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?
所以现在是我们的错。
SO NOW IT'S OUR FAULT.
不，不是你的错。
NO, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
我只是想找到尸体。
I JUST WANT TO FIND THE BODY.
我给太平间打电话。
I'LL CALL THE MORGUE.
我已经查过太平间了；他不在那里。
I ALREADY CHECKED THE MORGUE;
HE'S NOT THERE.
哟，杰拉德！
YO, GERALD!
哟，我是托尼。
YO, IT'S TONY.
你那里有没有无人认领的尸体？
YOU HAVE ANY UNCLAIMED
BODIES DOWN THERE?
是的，她现在在这里。
YEAH, SHE'S HERE NOW.
等等，我问问。
HOLD ON, I'LL ASK.
这具尸体能放进焚化炉的滑道吗？
WOULD THIS BODY FIT DOWN
THE INCINERATOR CHUTE?
焚化炉？
THE INCINERATOR?
是的，她进去了。
YEAH, THAT GOT HER.
哟，谢谢，G。
YO, THANKS, G.
好的，我马上就下来。
OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
你真幸运。有人把
YOU'RE IN LUCK.
SOMEONE STUFFED
一个肥胖的尸体塞进了ICU的壁橱里。
SOME FAT STIFF IN THE
CLOSET OF THE I.C.U.
为什么？你为什么非走不可？
WHY? WHY DO YOU
HAVE TO GO?
我必须走。
I JUST GOT TO.
那急什么？
WELL, WHAT'S THE HURRY?
医生说没关系。
DOCTOR SAID
IT WAS OKAY.
嗯，会没事的。
WELL, IT WILL BE OKAY.
他必须先缝好。
HE HAS TO STITCH IT UP FIRST.
而且，我喜欢你在身边。
BESIDES, I LIKE HAVING
YOU AROUND.
今天这里没什么有趣的人。
THERE'S NOT VERY MANY
INTERESTING PEOPLE HERE TODAY.
所以，也许…我还会回来的。
SO, MAYBE...
I'LL COME BACK.
来吧，你得帮我。
COME ON, YOU'VE GOT
TO HELP ME OUT.
你不想让我惹麻烦，对吧？
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET ME
IN TROUBLE, DO YOU?
我给你写张条子。
I'LL WRITE YOU A NOTE.
此外，你绝对不想让它感染，相信我。
BESIDES, YOU DO NOT WANT TO GET
THAT INFECTED, BELIEVE ME.
看，就几分钟。
LOOK, JUST A FEW MINUTES.
我去找个医生，我们会处理的。
I'LL GET A DOCTOR,
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
好吧。
ALL RIGHT.
好的。
GOOD.
嘿，莱内特。是的。
HEY, LYNETTE.
YEAH.
你能帮我找一下这个男孩的母亲吗？
COULD YOU GET THIS
BOY'S MOTHER FOR ME?
哦。他18岁了。
OH. HE'S 18.
是的，但他是帮派成员——被捅伤了。
YEAH, BUT HE'S
A GANGBANGER--
GOT STABBED.
我担心他会逃跑去报复。马克。
I'M AFRAID HE'S GOING TO BOLT
TO SETTLE THE SCORE. MARK.
是啊，等一下。
YEAH, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
你承认血栓了吗？
YOU ADMITTING
THAT THROMBOSIS?
他股动脉有高级病变。
HE'S GOT A HIGH-GRADE LESION
IN THE FEMORAL ARTERY.
我知道。你带他上去吗？
I KNOW. YOU TAKING HIM UP?
嗯，我需要向罗马诺汇报
WELL, I NEED TO PRESENT
HIM TO ROMANO
然后我们会把整个团队都叫下来。
AND THEN WE'LL BRING
DOWN THE WHOLE TEAM.
什么时候？尽快。
WHEN?
AS SOON AS I CAN.
马克，你能缝合我的人吗？
MARK, CAN YOU
STITCH UP MY GUY?
他开始焦躁不安了。我马上就到。
HE'S GETTING ANTSY.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
听着，珍妮，你能帮我清一下这个脖子吗？
LOOK, JEANIE,
CAN YOU CLEAR THIS NECK FOR ME?
他看起来没事。单车事故。
HE LOOKS OKAY.
SINGLE VEHICLE M.V.A.
我点了外伤检查组。好的，没问题。
I ORDERED A TRAUMA PANEL.
SURE, YOU GOT IT.
谢谢。当然。
THANK YOU.
SURE.
这里怎么样？
HOW WE DOING IN HERE?
生命体征正常。
VITALS ARE NORMAL.
我很好。
I'M FINE.
你失去知觉了吗，利普森先生？
DID YOU LOSE CONSCIOUSNESS,
MR. LIPSON?
没有。听着，我告诉他们这真的没必要。
NO. LISTEN, I TOLD THEM
THIS REALLY WASN'T NECESSARY.
胸部或腹部疼痛吗？
ANY CHEST OR
ABDOMINAL PAIN?
我能回家吗？
CAN I GO HOME?
不。我们得先给你拍个颈部X光片。
NO. WE NEED TO GET AN X-RAY
OF YOUR NECK FIRST.
你以前得过肝炎吗？
HAVE YOU EVER HAD HEPATITIS?
我不这么认为。为什么？
I DON'T THINK SO. WHY?
你的眼睛有点黄。
YOUR EYES
ARE A LITTLE YELLOW.
有在服用任何药物吗？
ON ANY MEDICATION?
强的松、环孢素、依木兰。
PREDNISONE, CYCLOSPORIN,
IMURAN.
那些是移植药物。
THOSE ARE
TRANSPLANT MEDS.
嗯，我两年前换了新肝脏。
WELL, I HAD A NEW LIVER
TWO YEARS AGO.
好的。我们测个凝血酶原时间
OKAY. LET'S GET
A PROTIME
肝功能检查和环孢素水平。
L.F.T.s AND A
CYCLOSPORIN LEVEL.
有问题吗？
SOMETHING'S WRONG?
医生，医生，请过来。
DOCTOR, DOCTOR,
POR FAVOR VENGA.
就一分钟。你黄疸了。
JUST ONE MINUTE.
YOU'RE JAUNDICED.
出了个错误。你得纠正它。
HUBO UN EQUIVOCACION.
LO TIENE QUE COMPONER.
我们现在就需要做那些检查。
WE NEED TO DO
THOSE TESTS NOW.
我马上回来。
I'LL BE BACK.
她告诉女士她没有我的号码。
LE DIJERA A LA SENORA
QUE NO TENIA MI NUMERO.
但我表姐给我带来了我的卡。
PERO MI PRIMA
ME TRAJO MI TARJETA.
孩子需要它才能接受治疗。
EL NIÑO LO NECESITA
PARA RECIBIR TRATAMIENTO.
好的，就这样…
OKAY, JUST...
谢谢。
THANKS.
别担心，卡门。我来了。
NO TE PREOCUPES, CARMEN.
YA LLEGUE.
嗯，这是…这是你的卡。
UM, THIS-THIS IS YOUR CARD.
罗莎·穆尼奥斯。
ROSA MUÑOZ.
是。是社…社会保障卡。
SI. ES SOCIAL...
SOCIAL SECURITY CARD.
她说她的名字是卡门。
SHE SAID HER
NAME WAS CARMEN.
罗莎·卡门，是。
ROSA CARMEN, SI.
你叫什么名字？
AND YOUR NAME?
路易莎。
LUISA.
她的姐姐？
HER SISTER?
表…嗯，表姐妹。
PRI... UM, COUSINS.
好的。我理解你对安吉尔健康的担忧，
OKAY. I UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU'RE CONCERNED
但这将是欺诈。
FOR ANGEL'S HEALTH,
BUT THIS WOULD BE FRAUD.
他是不是非法移民无关紧要。
IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF HE'S ILLEGAL.
哦，不，不，不。那是她的号码。
OH, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S HER NUMBER.
不，这是你的卡。
NO, THIS IS YOUR CARD.
不。
NO.
不。告诉他他需要一个特殊的医生…
NO. DILE QUE EL NECESITA
DOCTOR ESPECIAL...
不。嗯…
NO. UM...
她说他需要一个特殊的医生？
SHE SAY THAT HE NEED
A SPECIAL DOCTOR?
心脏病专家。安吉尔的心脏可能有问题。
A CARDIOLOGIST. THERE
COULD BE A PROBLEM
WITH ANGEL'S HEART.
请收下这个号码。
PLEASE TAKE THIS NUMBER.
拜托了。其他医院不收他…
PLEASE. OTHER HOSPITAL
NO TAKE HIM...
女士。穆尼奥斯，我们是县医院。
MRS. MUÑOZ, WE'RE
A COUNTY HOSPITAL.
我们治疗所有急诊病例。
WE TREAT ALL EMERGENCIES.
真的吗？
TRUE?
真的。
TRUE.
有时床位不足时
SOMETIMES WHEN WE'RE
SHORT ON BEDS
我们会把尸体放在储藏室里。
WE STICK THE BODIES
IN THE STORAGE ROOM.
你为什么不给我们打电话？我们打了。
WHY DIDN'T YOU CALL US?
WE DID.
伙计们，我得回去了。
YOU GUYS, I GOT TO GET BACK.
嗯，你是想把他带回去还是我来？
WELL, DO YOU WANT TO TAKE HIM
BACK OR SHOULD I?
他是黑人。
HE'S BLACK.
那有问题吗？
THAT A PROBLEM?
达娜·埃利斯——她怎么样？
DANA ELLIS-- WHAT ABOUT HER?
嗯，我担心幻肢痛。
WELL, I'M WORRIED
ABOUT PHANTOM LIMB PAIN.
嗯，别担心——她打了吗啡。
WELL, DON'T BE--
SHE'S ON MORPHINE.
那没用。
THAT'S NOT GOING TO DO IT.
我想给她做预防性镇痛，重新连接运动神经。
I WANT TO PUT HER ON A
PREEMPTIVE ANALGESIA TO
REWIRE THE MOTOR NERVES.
我不知道她还是你的病人。
I DIDN'T REALIZE
SHE WAS STILL YOUR PATIENT.
罗马诺医生，格林医生
DR. ROMANO, DR. GREENE IS
ON LINE THREE FROM THE E.R.
在急诊室三号线等一个缺血性腿的会诊。
WAITING ON A CONSULT
ON AN ISCHEMIC LEG.
他有多普勒搏动吗？
DOES HE HAVE
A PULSE BY DOPPLER?
我查一下。
I'LL CHECK.
只是一个简单的腰椎硬膜外麻醉。
IT'S A SIMPLE
LUMBAR EPIDURAL.
只会让手术推迟几天。
IT'S ONLY GOING
TO HAVE TO PUT THE
SURGERY OFF A FEW DAYS.
听着，我讨厌告诉你
LOOK, I HATE TO BE THE ONE
TO TELL YOU
但一个晚间课程并不能让你成为疼痛管理专家。
BUT ONE NIGHT COURSE DOES NOT A
PAIN MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST MAKE.
是的，病人有多普勒搏动。
YES, THE PATIENT
HAS A DOPPLER PULSE.
格林医生想要一个预计到达时间。
DR. GREENE WANTS
AN E.T.A.
等我到那里。
WHEN I GET THERE.
没有理由不尝试，好吗？
THERE'S NO REASON
NOT TO TRY IT,
ALL RIGHT?
我不知道她心理上是否准备好接受手术。
I DON'T KNOW THAT SHE'S
PSYCHOLOGICALLY READY
FOR THE SURGERY.
三天不会有太大区别。
THREE DAYS ISN'T GOING TO MAKE
MUCH DIFFERENCE.
戴尔，那个新实习生表现怎么样？
DALE, HOW'S THAT NEW INTERN
WORKING OUT?
她会适应的。
SHE'LL GET
THE HANG OF IT.
你为什么不让她休息一下
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE HER A BREAK
让她参与这个穿孔憩室手术呢。
AND LET HER SCRUB IN
ON THIS PERFED TIC.
我要和家属谈谈。嘿，不，你不能。
I'M GOING TO TALK
TO THE FAMILY.
HEY, NO, YOU'RE NOT.
那个女孩腿上有肿瘤，我不会坐视不理
THAT GIRL HAS A TUMOR IN HER LEG
AND I WON'T SIT IDLY BY
让你实验你上周刚读到的一些技术。
SO YOU CAN EXPERIMENT
WITH SOME TECHNIQUE
我担心
YOU JUST READ ABOUT
LAST WEEK.
I'M WORRIED
她会感觉到不存在的腿的疼痛。
THAT SHE'LL FEEL
PAIN IN A LEG
THAT ISN'T THERE.
罗马诺医生。什么？！
DR. ROMANO.
WHAT?!
也许你应该和格林医生谈谈。
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TALK
TO DR. GREENE.
他想要更明确的东西。
HE WANTS SOMETHING
MORE DEFINITIVE.
如果那家伙小腿疼痛，告诉他做超声波。
IF THE GUY'S GOT CALF PAIN,
TELL HIM TO DO AN ULTRASOUND.
嘿，别走开。
HEY, DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
排除深静脉血栓。
AND RULE OUT D.V.T.
那会让他安静一段时间的。
THAT'LL SHUT HIM UP
FOR A WHILE.
别管了，罗斯！
LEAVE IT ALONE, ROSS!
嘿，卡罗尔，我得去楼上参加这个面试。
HEY, CAROL, I HAVE TO HEAD
UPSTAIRS TO THIS INTERVIEW.
罗马诺一出现，你就给我传呼，好吗？
WILL YOU PAGE ME
THE SECOND ROMANO DECIDES
嘿，别抱太大希望。
TO GRACE US
WITH HIS PRESENCE?
别动。
HEY, DON'T HOLD YOUR BREATH.
你会撕裂你的缝线。
HOLD STILL.
YOU'LL TEAR YOUR STITCHES.
你让我出去好吗？
WOULD YOU LET ME
OUT OF HERE?
我得走了。为什么？为什么？
I GOT TO GO.
WHY? WHY?
所以你可以照顾那个对你做这种事的人吗？
SO YOU CAN TAKE CARE OF THE GUY
THAT DID THIS TO YOU?
嘿，发生什么事了？
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
波想报复。
BO HERE WANTS TO RETALIATE.
你说医生给我缝好后我就可以走了！
YOU SAID THAT
DOCTOR STITCHED ME
UP AND THEN I CAN GO!
我们只是想让你安全，波。
WE JUST WANT YOU
TO BE SAFE, BO.
是啊，算了吧，女士。
YEAH, WELL,
SAVE IT LADY.
听着，夫人，谢谢你治好我。
LOOK, MA'AM, THANKS
FOR FIXING ME.
我要走了。嘿，等等！
I'M GOING.
HEY, WAIT!
如果你想让我签什么，我就签！
IF YOU WANT ME TO SIGN
SOMETHING, I'LL SIGN IT!
别那样做！你会把你的血管撕开的。
DON'T DO THAT!
YOU'LL RIP YOUR VEIN OPEN.
我不想让你到处流血。
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE YOU
BLEEDING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
那就拿出来。好的。
THEN TAKE
IT OUT.
OKAY.
你想离开那么急吗？没关系。
YOU WANT TO LEAVE THAT BAD?
THAT'S FINE.
我去找合适的工具，把它取出来
LET ME GET THE RIGHT INSTRUMENT,
I'LL TAKE IT OUT
你可以去忙你的事了。
YOU CAN GO ABOUT YOUR BUSINESS.
请在这里等一下。等一分钟就好。
PLEASE JUST WAIT HERE.
JUST WAIT ONE MINUTE.
我马上回来。
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
发生什么事了？
WHAT'S GOING ON?
我们不能让他走。
WE CAN'T
LET HIM LEAVE.
那他妈妈什么时候来？
WELL, WHEN'S THE
MOTHER GETTING HERE?
还没联系上她。
HAVEN'T REACHED HER YET.
我给精神科打电话。
I'M CALLING DOWN PSYCH.
到时候他会走了。
HE'LL BE GONE BY THEN.
那是什么？
WHAT IS THAT?
咪达唑仑。我得给他注射镇静剂
VERSED. I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO SEDATE HIM
直到他妈妈来。
TILL THE MOTHER
GETS HERE.
如果不是完全不道德的话，那可能是一个选择。
THAT MIGHT BE AN OPTION
IF IT WASN'T TOTALLY UNETHICAL.
哦，别人的生命危在旦夕可不行。
OH, NOT WITH SOMEONE'S
LIFE AT STAKE.
你不能用药物束缚别人。
YOU CAN'T RESTRAIN SOMEONE
WITH DRUGS.
他很激动。
HE WAS AGITATED.
为了完成治疗，我们必须给他注射镇静剂。
TO FINISH THE TREATMENT,
WE HAD TO SEDATE HIM.
安保人员可以把他留在这里，直到精神科把他拘留。
SECURITY CAN KEEP HIM DOWN HERE
UNTIL PSYCH PUTS HIM ON HOLD.
他们必须证明
THEY'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO PROVE
这孩子对他人有危险。
THAT THE KID IS
A DANGER TO OTHERS.
他了解系统。他只会撒谎。
HE KNOWS THE SYSTEM.
HE'LL JUST LIE.
嗯，也许到时候我们会找到他妈妈。
WELL, MAYBE WE'LL FIND
HIS MOTHER BY THEN.
我来确保。
I'M GOING TO MAKE SURE.
不用那个。
NOT WITH THAT.
你有更好的主意吗？
YOU HAVE A BETTER IDEA?
我来处理。
I'LL HANDLE IT.
你知道如果你不这么做，
YOU KNOW WHAT
HE'LL DO
他会怎么做。
IF YOU DON'T.
我理解你的动机
I UNDERSTAND
YOUR MOTIVE
我知道我向你寻求了帮助。
AND I KNOW I ASKED
FOR YOUR HELP.
你为什么不专注于门诊病人呢？
WHY DON'T YOU STICK WITH
THE CLINIC PATIENTS.
急诊室的病人留给我，好吗？
LEAVE THE E.R. ONES
TO ME, ALL RIGHT?
祝你好运。
GOOD LUCK.
嗯，我不想你再来到这里…也许会死。
WELL, I DON'T WANT
YOU ENDING UP HERE
AGAIN... MAYBE DEAD.
如果事情那样发展，就这样发展吧。
IF IT GOES DOWN LIKE THAT,
IT GOES DOWN LIKE THAT.
这不是第一次了。
IT WOULDN'T BE
THE FIRST TIME.
你不是那个意思。
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
哟！这个临时警察在这里干什么？
YO! WHAT'S
THE RENT-A-COP DOING HERE?
我希望你能和某人谈谈。
I WANT YOU TO
BE ABLE TO TALK
TO SOMEBODY.
该死！我信任你。
DAMN! I TRUSTED YOU.
嘿，我只是想帮你。
HEY, I'M JUST TRYING
TO HELP YOU.
算了吧，女士。我不会和任何人说话的。
SAVE IT, LADY.
I AIN'T TALKING TO NOBODY.
好的。我们会等到你妈妈来。
OKAY. WE'LL JUST WAIT
UNTIL YOUR MOM GETS HERE.
我妈妈？什么，你给我妈妈打电话了？
MY MOM? WHAT,
YOU CALLED MY MOM?
我马上回来。
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
别让他走。
DON'T LET HIM LEAVE.
罗马诺：注意，戴尔。
Romano:
PAY ATTENTION, DALE.
彼得是附近最快的结肠解剖者之一
PETER IS ONE OF
THE FASTEST COLON
DISSECTORS AROUND
现在莉齐的枪暂时收起来了。
NOW THAT LIZZIE'S GUN'S
IN THE HOLSTER FOR A WHILE.
好吧。我们有一个开腹手术，各位。
ALL RIGHT. WE'VE GOT
AN OPEN ABDOMEN, PEOPLE.
请加快速度。
LET'S TURN UP
THE HEAT, PLEASE.
伊丽莎白，你能不能牵拉降结肠
ELIZABETH, WOULD YOU RETRACT
THE DESCENDING COLON
当我分离腹膜反折时？
WHILE I FREE UP
THE PERITONEAL REFLECTION?
我很乐意。
MY PLEASURE.
呃，实际上，戴尔，你为什么不牵拉电凝刀
UH, ACTUALLY,
DALE, WHY DON'T YOU
RETRACT THE BOVIE
把吸引器给莉齐。
AND GIVE LIZZIE
THE SUCKER.
好的。莉齐，你能把这个渗血区域吸出来吗？
RIGHT. LIZZIE, SUCK OUT
THIS OOZING AREA, WOULD YOU?
如果你不介意，我从来不喜欢被叫做莉齐。
IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I'VE NEVER CARED FOR
BEING CALLED LIZZIE.
戴尔：罗马诺医生一直都这么叫你。
Dale:
DR. ROMANO CALLS YOU THAT
ALL THE TIME.
本顿：戴尔，我正在解剖什么结构？
Benton:
DALE, WHAT STRUCTURE
AM I DISSECTING?
呃，髂腹股沟神经。
UH, ILEOINGUINAL NERVE.
哦，天哪。
OH, BOY.
伊丽莎白，你能不能
ELIZABETH, WOULD YOU
帮他一下？
HELP HIM OUT, PLEASE?
由于轻微的蠕动
OWING TO THE SLIGHT PERISTALSIS
是左输尿管。
IT'S THE LEFT URETER.
吸得快一点，
BETTER GET
A LITTLE FASTER
莉齐。
WITH THAT SUCTION, LIZZIE.
本顿：好的。我分离了乙状结肠。
Benton:
OKAY. I'VE FREED THE SIGMOID.
伊丽莎白，你能不能结扎近端
ELIZABETH, WOULD YOU
LIGATE THE PROXIMAL SIDE
我同时从下方钳夹血管？
WHILE I CLAMP THE VESSELS
FROM BELOW, PLEASE?
当然。
CERTAINLY.
戴尔，让开。让我冲洗。
DALE, MOVE OVER.
LET ME IRRIGATE.
罗马诺：我更喜欢戴尔做任何结扎。
Romano:
I'D PREFER DALE
DO ANY LIGATING.
抱歉打扰你，罗马诺医生
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU,
DR. ROMANO
但格林医生又打电话来了。
BUT DR. GREENE
IS CALLING AGAIN.
哎呀。莉齐，我想你刚刚
OOPS. LIZZIE, I
THINK YOU JUST
污染了自己。
CONTAMINATED
YOURSELF.
我没有。
I DID NOT.
小心为妙；换个手术服。
BETTER BE SAFE;
CHANGE GOWNS.
我没有污染自己。
I DIDN'T CONTAMINATE MYSELF.
我看到了。她很干净。
I SAW IT.
SHE'S CLEAN.
谢谢你。所以别欺负她。
THANK YOU.
SO DON'T
PICK ON HER.
莉齐，去洗手
LIZZIE, SCRUB OUT
然后去安抚格林，好吗？
AND GO PACIFY GREENE,
WOULD YOU?
韦弗：嘿。你还在。
Weaver:
HEY. YOU'RE STILL HERE.
是的。
YEAH.
你为儿科急诊室付出了很多努力，我承认。
YOU'RE PUTTING
A LOT OF EFFORT
嗯，我接受。
INTO THIS PEDES E.R.,
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
嘿，伙计们。嘿。
WELL, I'LL TAKE IT.
这是我们新的儿科急诊室主治医生
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
和全职送货员，道格·罗斯。
THIS IS OUR NEW
PEDES E.R. ATTENDING
你有什么给我们？
AND FULL-TIME
DELIVERY BOY, DOUG ROSS.
你被禁了。他给的小费很差。
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FOR US?
格林：这是克劳迪娅·奥尔森。
YOU'RE CUT OFF.
HE'S A BAD TIPPER.
她是
Greene:
THIS IS CLAUDIA OLSEN.
SHE'S ONE
急诊医学主任的候选人之一。
OF THE CANDIDATES FOR
CHIEF OF EMERGENCY MEDICINE.
罗斯：哦，一个受虐狂？
Ross:
OH, A MASOCHIST?
奥尔森：是的。
Olsen:
YEAH.
凯利·韦弗。
KERRY WEAVER.
临时主任。
THE INTERIM CHIEF.
是啊。很高兴见到你。
YEAH. IT'S NICE
TO MEET YOU.
我想你今天也在面试。
I TAKE IT YOU'RE
INTERVIEWING
TODAY AS WELL.
（笑）：你怎么猜到的？
( laughing ):
HOW DID YOU GUESS?
嗯，至少我先来了。
WELL, AT LEAST
I GOT TO GO FIRST.
很高兴见到你。
IT WAS NICE
TO MEET YOU.
你也是。
YOU, TOO.
珍妮：可能是肝炎
Jeanie:
IT COULD BE HEPATITIS
但我们主要担心的是你正在排斥肝脏。
BUT OUR MAJOR CONCERN IS THAT
YOU'RE REJECTING THE LIVER.
嗯，我感觉很好；有点累。
WELL, I FEEL FINE;
A LITTLE TIRED.
你有没有忘记吃药？
DO YOU EVER FORGET
TO TAKE YOUR MEDS?
没有。我每天都设定闹钟。
NO. I SET MY WATCH DAILY.
我的环孢素水平在治疗范围内，不是吗？
MY CYCLOSPORIN LEVEL'S
THERAPEUTIC, ISN'T IT?
嗯哼。我想我们应该安排一次肝活检。
MM-HMM. I THINK WE
SHOULD ARRANGE FOR
A LIVER BIOPSY.
如果对你来说都一样
IF IT'S ALL THE SAME TO YOU
我真的宁愿去看我自己的医生。
I WOULD REALLY RATHER SEE
MY OWN DOCTOR.
我理解，但他没有告诉你什么吗
I UNDERSTAND,
BUT HE HASN'T SAID
ANYTHING TO YOU
关于你异常的肝功能检查？
ABOUT YOUR
ABNORMAL L.F.T.s?
没有。我忙起来了；错过了几次体检。
NO. I GOT BUSY;
MISSED A COUPLE OF CHECKUPS.
嗯，我确定你知道随访有多重要
WELL, I'M SURE YOU
KNOW HOW IMPORTANT
FOLLOW-UPS ARE
器官移植后。
AFTER ORGAN
TRANSPLANTATION.
我想我心里总是有所怀疑
I THINK PART OF ME
ALWAYS SUSPECTED
但不想确定。
BUT DIDN'T WANT
TO KNOW FOR SURE.
现在我确定了。
NOW I DO.
你总可以再次把自己列入UNOS名单。
YOU CAN ALWAYS PUT
YOURSELF ON THE
UNOS LIST AGAIN.
我不这么认为。
I DON'T THINK SO.
第二次？
SECOND TIME AROUND?
你第一次就合格了。
YOU QUALIFIED
THE FIRST TIME.
你永远不知道。你可能会再次幸运。
YOU NEVER KNOW.
YOU COULD GET
LUCKY AGAIN.
嗨。
HI.
你有穆尼奥斯家的孩子吗？
YOU HAVE THE
MUNOZ KID?
我有。是的。再打扰一下。打扰一下。
I DO. YES. EXCUSE
ME ONE MORE TIME.
EXCUSE ME.
是心肌病吗？
IS IT CARDIOMYOPATHY?
这孩子需要进行全面的电生理检查。
THE BOY'S GOING TO NEED
A FULL E.P. WORKUP.
他有异位搏动吗？
DID HE HAVE
AN ECTOPY?
没有，超声心动图排除了出口梗阻。
NO, AND THE ECHO RULED OUT
AN OUTLET OBSTRUCTION.
所以他昏厥的原因是…？
SO THE CAUSE
OF HIS FAINTING...?
一起：很可能是心律失常。
Together:
IT'S PROBABLY ARRHYTHMIA.
我打算在导管室诱导它
I'M GOING TO TRY TO INDUCE IT
IN THE CATH LAB
如果这样的话，他马上就需要一个
AND IF SO,
HE'S GOING TO NEED
体内植入式心律转复除颤器。
AN INTERNAL CARDIOVERTER
DEFIBRILLATOR RIGHT AWAY.
好的。很高兴我们发现了。
OKAY. I'M GLAD
WE CAUGHT IT.
是的。我给心脏外科医生打电话。你能取得同意吗？
YEAH. I'LL CALL
A CARDIAC SURGEON.
CAN YOU GET CONSENT?
好的。谢谢你。
SURE. THANK YOU.
别谢我。孩子需要。
DON'T THANK ME.
THE KID NEEDS IT.
是啊。
YEAH.
非常感谢，非常感谢。
MUCHISIMAS GRACIAS,
MUCHISIMAS GRACIAS.
他终于要得到他需要的治疗了。
POR FIN VA RECIBIR
EL TRATAMIENTO
QUE NECISITA.
愿上帝保佑你。
QUE DIOS LA BENDIGA.
是时候了。罗马诺在哪儿？
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
WHERE'S ROMANO?
只有我，恐怕。
JUST ME, I'M AFRAID.
那么，你能收他入院吗？
SO, CAN YOU ADMIT HIM?
基于我的其他职责，我得说不能。
BASED ON MY OTHER
RESPONSIBILITIES,
I'D SAY NO.
所以你在这里拖延我？
SO YOU'RE HERE
TO STALL ME?
差不多吧。
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
没关系。我让他通过放射科。
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL PASS HIM THROUGH RADIOLOGY.
他反正需要做血管造影
HE NEEDS
AN ANGIOGRAM ANYWAY
但告诉罗马诺你只给他争取了20分钟。
BUT TELL ROMANO
YOU ONLY BOUGHT
HIM 20 MINUTES.
不要让病人待太久。
DON'T LEAVE THE
PATIENT THERE TOO LONG.
如果外科医生反应迟钝，放射科医生
RADIOLOGISTS SNATCH
THE PROCEDURES
FOR THEMSELVES
会抢走手术。
IF THE SURGEONS ARE
SLOW ON THE UPTAKE.
知道了。谢谢你。
NOTED. THANK YOU.
是吗？呃，珍妮？
YEAH?
UH, JEANIE?
谁？这是你M.P.A.的血酒精浓度。
ON WHO?
HERE'S THE B.A.
ON YOUR M.P.A.
利普森；创伤二科。
LIPSON; TRAUMA TWO.
我没有点血酒精浓度。
I DIDN'T ORDER A B.A.
我点了。这是创伤检查组的一部分。兰迪放在我盒子里了。
I DID. IT'S PART
OF THE TRAUMA PANEL.
RANDI PUT IT IN MY BOX.
嘿…有什么不对劲吗？
HEY...
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
血酒精浓度是0.04。
BLOOD ALCOHOL'S .04.
这远低于法定限制。
THAT'S WELL BELOW
THE LEGAL LIMIT.
那仍然意味着他喝过酒。
IT STILL MEANS
HE'S BEEN DRINKING.
我完成了眩晕的报告——
I FINISHED MY WRITE-UP
ON THE VERTIGO--
我想这只是病毒感染——我给你带了咖啡。
I THINK IT'S JUST A VIRUS--
AND I GOT YOU SOME COFFEE.
你不需要那样做。
YOU DON'T NEED
TO DO THAT.
嗯，我反正去自助餐厅找点东西。
WELL, I WAS DOWN
IN THE CAFETERIA
好的。谢谢。
LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING ANYWAY.
我告诉你。
ALL RIGHT. THANKS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
你为什么不去给
WHY DON'T YOU START THE I.V.
ON THE FOUR-YEAR-OLD
帘子后面那个四岁肠胃炎的孩子打静脉针——
WITH GASTROENTERITIS
IN CURTAIN ONE--
500毫升生理盐水推注——但要小心。
500cc BOLUS OF SALINE--
BUT BE CAREFUL.
她脱水了。可能有点困难。
SHE'S DEHYDRATED.
COULD BE TRICKY.
好的。
RIGHT.
嘿，非常感谢。我感觉好多了。
HEY, THANKS A LOT.
I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER.
很高兴听到。
GLAD TO HEAR IT.
如果你想要免费的我的演出票，给我打电话。
CALL ME IF YOU'D
LIKE SOME FREE
TICKETS TO MY SHOW.
谢谢你。
THANK YOU.
哦！
OOH!
你还好吗？
ARE YOU OKAY?
那是怎么回事？
HOW'D THAT GET THERE?
给你。
THERE YOU GO.
我只是不想让你的东西消失。再见。
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
THINGS DISAPPEARING
ON YOU. SEE YOU.
对了，你有没有碰巧看到一具尸体…？
SAY, YOU HAVEN'T, BY ANY CHANCE,
SEEN A BOD...?
哦，卡罗尔，你能帮我打静脉针吗？
OH, CAROL, COULD YOU
HELP ME START AN I.V.?
她脱水了。
SHE'S DEHYDRATED.
I DON'T WANT TO
HURT THE KID.
还没。你试过了吗？
NOT YET.
HAVE YOU TRIED?
所以你还没打过静脉针？
SO YOU HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED
AN I.V. YET?
老实说？没有。
HONESTLY? NO.
这太荒谬了，露西。每个人都认为你能。
THIS IS RIDICULOUS, LUCY.
EVERYONE THINKS YOU CAN.
我知道。我今天会和卡特医生谈谈。
I KNOW. I'M GOING TO
TALK TO DR. CARTER TODAY.
嗯，如果你不，我就去。
WELL, IF YOU DON'T, I WILL.
嘿！嘿！
HEY! HEY!
发生什么事了？
WHAT HAPPENED?
他跑了。
HE TOOK OFF.
我看到了。你本该阻止他的。
I CAN SEE THAT. YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO STOP HIM.
无法说服他。
THERE WAS NO
TALKING HIM DOWN.
你本不该谈判。
YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED
TO NEGOTIATE.
你本该阻止他离开。
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO
STOP HIM FROM LEAVING.
在你们把他拘留前，我不能把他留在这里。
I CAN'T KEEP HIM HERE
UNTIL YOU GET THE HOLD.
他不知道。
HE DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
抱歉。
SORRY.
罗斯：别动。我想固定这个导管。
Ross:
HOLD STILL.
I WANT TO SECURE THIS CATHETER.
坚持住。做得很好。
HANG ON. DOING GREAT.
还要多久？
HOW MUCH LONGER?
再等一下。就一秒钟。
A LITTLE BIT.
JUST A SECOND HERE.
好的。现在，你要翻回到背上，好吗？
OKAY. NOW, YOU'RE GOING TO ROLL
BACK OVER ON YOUR BACK, OKAY?
轻轻地。
NICE AND EASY.
需要多久才能起作用？
HOW LONG DOES
IT TAKE TO WORK?
大约20分钟才能完全起效。
ABOUT 20 MINUTES
FOR THE FULL EFFECT.
不过，你很快就会开始感觉到东西了。
YOU'RE GOING TO START FEELING
THINGS PRETTY SOON, THOUGH.
我会给你安排一个六天疗程——
I'M GOING TO PUT YOU
ON A SIX-DAY CYCLE--
手术前三天，手术后三天，用于滴注。
THREE DAYS BEFORE THE SURGERY,
THREE DAYS AFTER, FOR THE DRIP.
罗马诺医生。
DR. ROMANO.
罗斯医生。
DR. ROSS.
嗨，达娜。
HI, DANA.
我决定要硬膜外麻醉。
I DECIDED I
WANTED THE EPIDURAL.
你决定了？
YOU DID?
你当时在手术室
YOU WERE IN SURGERY
所以我解释了程序。
SO I EXPLAINED
THE PROTOCOL.
那她的父母呢？
AND THE PARENTS?
他们同意了。
THEY'RE ON BOARD.
太棒了。
TERRIFIC.
你有一分钟吗？
YOU GOT A SECOND?
当然。好的。
SURE. ALL RIGHT.
我马上回来。
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
你做得很好。
YOU DID GREAT.
恭喜你。你只是推迟了手术。
CONGRATULATIONS. YOU JUST
POSTPONED THE SURGERY.
你没有给我太多选择。
YOU DIDN'T GIVE ME
A LOT OF OPTIONS.
那个儿科主治医生的事情刚刚发生。
THAT PEDES ATTENDING THING
JUST BARELY HAPPENED.
我投票赞成是因为我想
I VOTED FOR IT
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
“这家伙是个独行侠；偶尔会带来一些变化。”
"THE GUY'S A MAVERICK;
SHAKE THINGS UP EVERY
ONCE IN A WHILE."
但如果你想扮演约翰·韦恩
BUT IF YOU WANT TO
PLAY JOHN WAYNE
去急诊室，别在这里，我的病人这里。
DO IT DOWN IN THE
E.R. AND NOT UP HERE
WITH MY PATIENTS.
这个女孩处境非常脆弱。
THIS GIRL IS IN
A VERY VULNERABLE PLACE.
三天要求不多…
THREE DAYS IS NOT
A LOT TO ASK...
你没听我说，罗斯。
YOU'RE NOT
HEARING ME, ROSS.
这不是关于对错。
THIS IS NOT
ABOUT BEING RIGHT.
见鬼，我们都认为自己是对的。
HELL, WE ALL
THINK WE'RE RIGHT.
那并不能让你变得特别。
IT DOESN'T MAKE
YOU SPECIAL.
好的。
FINE.
你是在父母同意协议之前还是之后
DID YOU GIVE THE
KID A CHEESEBURGER
给那孩子吃了汉堡包？
BEFORE OR AFTER THE
PARENTS AGREED TO
THE PROTOCOL?
我以为我可能需要24小时才能说服他们。
I THOUGHT I MIGHT
NEED 24 HOURS TO
TALK THEM INTO IT.
你确定你知道你在做什么吗？
ARE YOU SURE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
等等。让我拿个小一点的针。
HOLD ON. LET ME GET
A SMALLER GAUGE.
哦，嘿，你。
OH, HEY, YOU.
嗨。
HI.
我一直在找你。
I HAVE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU ALL OVER.
发生什么事了？你把我忘了？
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU FORGOT ABOUT ME?
嗯，我，呃…
WELL, I, UH...
不，我没忘你。
NO, I DIDN'T
FORGET ABOUT YOU.
我等了三个小时。
I HAVE BEEN WAITING
FOR THREE HOURS.
嗯…好的，我去了太平间。
UM... OKAY, I WENT
TO THE MORGUE.
我也是。他不在那里了。
ME, TOO. HE'S NOT
THERE ANYMORE.
不，他不在那里。
NO, HE IS NOT THERE.
你把他放哪儿了？
WHERE'D YOU PUT HIM?
呃，我不知道怎么…
UH, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO...
怎么什么？
HOW TO WHAT?
怎么告诉你我有多抱歉你的失去。
HOW TO TELL YOU HOW SORRY I AM
ABOUT YOUR LOSS.
谢谢你，但你把他放哪儿了？
THANK YOU,
BUT WHERE DID YOU PUT HIM?
我把他放哪儿了？
WHERE DID I PUT HIM?
你不记得了。
YOU DON'T REMEMBER.
我当然记得。
OF COURSE I REMEMBER.
嗯…我找不到你。
UM... I COULDN'T
FIND YOU.
我这里很忙
I GOT VERY BUSY HERE
所以我把你哥哥…
SO I PUT YOUR BROTHER...
我把他放哪儿了？
WHERE DID I PUT HIM?
放射科。
RADIOLOGY.
我把他放在放射科了
I PUT HIM IN RADIOLOGY
但他有点碍事，所以…
BUT HE WAS KIND OF
IN THE WAY THERE, SO...
我把他留在了…这里…
I LEFT HIM... HERE...
在大厅里。
IN THE HALL.
我很抱歉。
I'M SORRY.
没问题。
NO PROBLEM.
我不敢相信我没在那里看到他。嗯。
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DIDN'T SEE HIM THERE. HMM.
他很容易被忽略。
HE'S EASY TO MISS.
（叹气）
( sighing )
怎么了？
WHAT'S WRONG?
没什么。没有怀孕测试。
NOTHING. THERE AREN'T
ANY PREGNANCY TESTS.
我们怎么会没有怀孕测试呢？
HOW COULD WE BE OUT
OF PREGNANCY TESTS?
我不做库存。
I DON'T DO INVENTORY.
那不是指责。
IT WASN'T
AN ACCUSATION.
哦！那是什么？
OOH! WHAT IS
THAT ALL ABOUT?
什么？
WHAT?
围巾。你从哪里弄来的？
THE SCARF. WHERE'D
YOU GET IT?
在礼品店买的。你不觉得它有用吗？
GOT IT AT THE GIFT SHOP.
YOU DON'T THINK IT WORKS?
你的外套怎么了？
WHAT WAS WRONG
WITH YOUR JACKET?
我想尝试一些不同的东西。
I WANTED TO TRY
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
摘掉耳环。这让整个东西失去平衡。
LOSE THE EARRINGS.
IT'S THROWING THE
WHOLE THING OFF-BALANCE.
卡罗尔，卡罗尔。
CAROL, CAROL.
这只是我第二次尝试。我想我能成功。
IT'S ONLY MY SECOND STICK.
I THINK I CAN GET IT.
我不能让学生给十岁以下的孩子打静脉针。
I CAN'T HAVE STUDENTS
STARTING I.V.s ON KIDS
UNDER TEN YEARS OLD.
当然。你能替我做吗？
SURE.
CAN YOU DO
IT FOR ME?
有问题吗？
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
我只是希望有经验的工作人员给孩子
I JUST WANT EXPERIENCED
STAFF STARTING I.V.s
打静脉针。
ON KIDS.
这仍然是教学医院，不是吗？
THIS IS STILL A TEACHING
HOSPITAL, ISN'T IT?
直到他们给孩子造成痛苦。
UNTIL THEY INFLICT PAIN
ON CHILDREN.
卡特：露西很擅长静脉注射。给他看。
Carter:
LUCY'S GREAT AT I.V.s.
SHOW HIM.
这与露西无关。
THIS IS NOT ABOUT LUCY.
这是我正在制定的政策。
IT'S A POLICY I'M SETTING.
哦，你在制定政策。
OH, YOU'RE SETTING
A POLICY.
嗯…凡事都有第一次。
WELL... FIRST TIME
FOR EVERYTHING.
我也会急着离开这里。
I'D BE IN A HURRY TO
GET OUT OF HERE, TOO.
什么？
WHAT?
我们发现你移植的肝脏衰竭的原因——你一直在喝酒。
WE FOUND OUT WHY
YOUR TRANSPLANTED
你不会相信我的。
LIVER'S FAILING--
YOU'VE BEEN DRINKING.
一次。
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BELIEVE ME.
你说得对。
ONE TIME.
我不相信你。
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
我查过UNOS了
I CHECKED WITH UNOS
你已经上了另一个移植名单
AND YOU'VE BEEN
ON THE LIST FOR
ANOTHER TRANSPLANT
两个月了。
FOR TWO MONTHS.
什么？你把第一个给你的肝脏喝坏了
WHAT? THAT YOU DRANK
THROUGH THE FIRST
ONE THEY GAVE YOU
现在你想要另一个？
AND NOW YOU
WANT ANOTHER ONE?
算了吧。不是那样的。就一天。
COME ON. IT WASN'T LIKE THAT.
IT WAS JUST A DAY.
我儿子通过了律师考试。
MY SON PASSED
HIS BAR EXAMINATION.
我知道我正在排斥，所以我想那会有什么坏处？
I KNEW I WAS REJECTING, SO I
FIGURED WHAT COULD IT HURT?
我们早午餐时喝了香槟。就这样。我发誓。
WE HAD CHAMPAGNE
AT BRUNCH. THAT'S
IT. I SWEAR.
嗯，你从进来这里就一直在撒谎。
WELL, YOU'VE BEEN
LYING EVER SINCE
YOU CAME IN HERE.
拜托…你不能告诉UNOS。
PLEASE... YOU CAN'T TELL UNOS.
我真的别无选择。
I REALLY DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
等等，等等，等等。拜托，你为了我
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
PLEASE, YOU'RE DOING THIS TO ME
就一杯香槟？
OVER ONE GLASS OF CHAMPAGNE?
那个名单上还有很多人
THERE ARE PLENTY
OF PEOPLE ON THAT LIST
他们连香槟都没喝过。
WHO HAVEN'T HAD
ANY CHAMPAGNE.
如果我失去我的位置，我活不过六个月。
IF I LOSE MY PLACE,
I WON'T LAST SIX MONTHS.
你举报我
YOU REPORT ME
我就死了。
I'M DEAD.
我求你了。
I'M BEGGING YOU.
你坐电梯。
YOU TAKE THE EL.
谁当班？
WHO'S ON?
韦弗。她在楼上
WEAVER. SHE'S UPSTAIRS
面试急诊医学主任。
INTERVIEWING FOR CHIEF
OF EMERGENCY MEDICINE.
我以为她是主任。
I THOUGHT SHE WAS CHIEF.
你去哪儿了？
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
格林医生？
DR. GREENE?
他在楼上面试她。
HE'S UPSTAIRS
INTERVIEWING HER.
所以我们没有主治医生。
SO WE HAVE NO ATTENDINGS.
嘿，小心点，杰瑞。
HEY, WATCH IT, JERRY.
抱歉，罗斯医生。
SORRY, DR. ROSS.
他是主治医生吗？
IS HE AN ATTENDING?
嘿，听着，呃，通常我不会说什么
HEY, LISTEN, UH, NORMALLY
I WOULDN'T SAY ANYTHING
但你不觉得那身打扮有点不合适吗？
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
THAT ATTIRE IS A
LITTLE INAPPROPRIATE?
这是工作。
IT'S BUSINESS.
我正在帮助韦弗医生。
I WAS HELPING OUT
DR. WEAVER.
干得好，凯利。
IT WAS
A GREAT JOB, KERRY.
我们很幸运能拥有你。
WE'D BE LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU.
谢谢你。
THANK YOU.
我知道这只是形式，但谢谢你过来。
I KNOW IT WAS A FORMALITY,
BUT THANKS FOR COMING IN.
嗯，我很感谢这个机会。
WELL, I APPRECIATE
THE OPPORTUNITY.
你的演讲完全符合我们的预期。
YOUR PRESENTATION WAS
EVERYTHING WE EXPECTED.
谢谢你。
THANK YOU.
嘿，我送你下去。
HEY, I'LL WALK YOU DOWN.
进行得很顺利，凯利。
WENT GREAT, KERRY.
你不觉得饼图太多了吗？
YOU DON'T THINK THE PIE
CHARTS WERE TOO MUCH?
不，图表很好。
NO, CHARTS ARE GOOD.
是吗？还有其他人用吗？
YEAH? DID ANYBODY
ELSE USE THEM?
你是第一个。
YOU'RE THE FIRST.
如果我表现得太急切…
IF I CAME ACROSS
AS TOO EAGER...
不，非常棒，凯利。
NO, IT WENT TERRIFIC, KERRY.
谢谢你，马克。
THANK YOU, MARK.
我不知道该如何回答那个问题
I NEVER KNOW HOW TO
ANSWER THAT QUESTION
关于我的弱点和…
ABOUT MY WEAKNESSES AND...
嗯，我可以在那里帮助你。
WELL, I COULD HAVE
HELPED YOU OUT THERE.
那件皮夹克真好看。
THAT'S A NICE LEATHER JACKET.
不，我说我想做一些测试
NO, I SAID I WANTED
TO RUN SOME TESTS
但没有医疗补助我不能做。
BUT I CAN'T
WITHOUT MEDICAID.
怎么了？
WHAT'S WRONG?
啊。
AH.
你不知道这个病人是非法移民吗？
DIDN'T YOU KNOW THIS
PATIENT WAS ILLEGAL?
是的，我知道，但这无关紧要。
YES, I DID,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
哦，是的，这很重要。
OH, YES, IT MATTERS.
我们谈论的是价值数千美元的测试。
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
WORTH OF TESTS.
州政府不会支付。
THE STATE WON'T PAY.
所以你不会治疗他？
SO YOU WON'T TREAT HIM?
我给他一些β受体阻滞剂。
I'LL GIVE HIM
SOME BETA BLOCKERS.
他可能会突发心脏骤停。
HE COULD HAVE
A SUDDEN CARDIAC ARREST.
我们已经监测他三个小时了。
WE'VE BEEN MONITORING
HIM FOR THREE HOURS.
他没有心律失常。
HE'S HAD NO ARRHYTHMIAS.
这就是为什么我们需要电生理研究。
THAT'S WHY WE NEED
THE E.P. STUDIES.
他的父亲和哥哥都死于此病。
HIS FATHER AND BROTHER
HAVE ALREADY DIED FROM THIS.
你记录到心律失常了吗？
DID YOU DOCUMENT
AN ARRHYTHMIA?
没有，但是…
NO, BUT...
我无能为力了。
THERE IS NOTHING
ELSE THAT I CAN DO.
凯森医生，这个孩子可能会突然死亡，你知道的。
DR. KAYSON, THIS BOY COULD
DROP DEAD AND YOU KNOW IT.
嗯，很多人都会。
WELL, SO COULD A LOT OF PEOPLE.
他不是紧急情况。
HE'S NOT EMERGENT.
我很抱歉。
I'M SORRY.
但她答应了。
PERO ELLA PROMETIO.
你说他情况稳定。
YOU SAID HE WAS STABLE.
胳膊上有一处枪伤。
SINGLE G.S.W. TO THE ARM.
他以前是。
HE WAS.
他插管了，血压低。
HE'S INTUBATED
AND HYPOTENSIVE.
路上情况会变，好吗？
THINGS CHANGE
EN ROUTE, OKAY?
怎么了？
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
帮派枪战搞砸了。
BOTCHED
GANG SHOOTING.
他们已经准备好他了。
THEY WERE READY FOR HIM.
这是今天早上那个人吗？
IS THIS THE GUY
FROM THIS MORNING?
是的，他叫波。
YEAH, HIS NAME'S BO.
我们以为只是他的胳膊。
WE THOUGHT IT WAS
JUST HIS ARM.
他在车上晕倒了。
HE CRASHED IN THE RIG.
卡特，我们需要你的帮助。
CARTER, WE
NEED YOUR HELP.
来吧。
COME ON.
好吧，欢迎回来，波。
ALL RIGHT,
WELCOME BACK, BO.
好了，大家，听我数数。
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
ON MY COUNT.
一，二，三。
ONE, TWO, THREE.
你为什么没有重新联系？
WHY DIDN'T YOU RECONTACT?
情况变得很混乱。
THINGS GOT
PRETTY CRAZY.
卡罗尔，把他接上监护仪。
CAROL, PUT HIM
ON THE MONITOR.
韦弗：我们有什么？
Weaver:
WHAT DO WE GOT?
贯穿性枪伤。
THROUGH AND THROUGH G.S.W.
肱三头肌中部区域。
MID-TRICEP AREA.
卡特，继续。
RUN IT, CARTER.
右侧呼吸音减弱。
DECREASED BREATH SOUNDS
ON THE RIGHT.
气管向左移位。
TRACHEAL SHIFT TO THE LEFT.
张力性气胸。
TENSION PNEUMO.
血压降到70。
B.P.'s DOWN TO 70.
血氧饱和度89。需要一根14号针头…
PULSE OX 89.
NEED A 14-GAUGE NEEDLE...
该死！…在20毫升注射器上。
DAMN IT!
...ON A 20cc SYRINGE.
然后我需要一个36号的法国导管。
AND THEN I'M GOING
TO NEED A 36 FRENCH.
好的，你想要在第二肋间隙，
ALL RIGHT, YOU WANT
TO DECOMPRESS
锁骨中线减压。
IN THE SECOND INTERCOSTAL SPACE,
MID-CLAVICULAR LINE.
好的，脉搏越来越强了。
OKAY, PULSE IS
GETTING STRONGER.
露西，抽血气。
LUCY, GET A BLOOD GAS.
我来做。
I'LL DO IT.
不，没关系。
NO, THAT'S OKAY.
我今天早上教过她怎么做。
I SHOWED HER HOW TO
DO IT THIS MORNING.
十号刀片。
TEN BLADE.
把压力袋接上线。
GET THE PRESSURE BAG
ON THE LINE.
入口创伤
ENTRANCE WOUND
右腋中线。
RIGHT MID-AXILLARY LINE.
子弹穿过手臂进入胸部。
BULLET WENT THROUGH THE
ARM INTO THE CHEST.
你为什么不给他脱衣服？
WHY COULDN'T YOU
UNDRESS HIM?
我们得抓紧时间送他。
WE HAD TO SCOOP AND RUN.
卡特：胸管在哪里？
Carter:
WHERE'S THAT CHEST TUBE?
我不敢相信你没看到这个胸部伤口。
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T SEE
THIS CHEST WOUND.
现在不行，卡罗尔。
NOT NOW, CAROL.
我抽不了血气。
I CAN'T GET THE BLOOD GAS.
我来做。
I'LL DO IT.
好的，胸管已经插入。
ALL RIGHT,
CHEST TUBE IS IN.
没关系，露西。
THAT'S OKAY, LUCY.
那些可能很难。
THOSE CAN BE TOUGH.
过来这边，帮我接第二条线。
COME AROUND HERE, HELP ME
WITH THE SECOND LINE.
好的，50毫升出来了。
OKAY, 50cc's OUT.
我需要四乘四的纱布。
I NEED FOUR BY FOURS.
我需要弹性绷带。
I NEED ELASTOPLAST.
格林：我们给X光打电话，让他们送个便携式胸片下来。
Greene:
LET'S CALL X RAY AND GET
A PORTABLE CHEST DOWN HERE.
我抽到血气了。
I GOT THE BLOOD GAS.
血压升到100/70。
B.P.'s UP TO 100/70.
第二条线怎么样了？
HOW'S THAT SECOND
LINE COMING?
我不能。
I CAN'T.
移开帘子。你有更多的空间。
MOVE THE DRAPE.
YOU GOT MORE ROOM.
不，我不能。
NO, I CAN'T DO IT.
来吧，露西，专心点。
COME ON, LUCY, FOCUS.
我真的不能。
I REALLY CAN'T.
就像其他静脉注射一样。
IT'S LIKE
ANY OTHER I.V.
我没打过静脉针。我不知道怎么打。
I HAVEN'T STARTED AN I.V.
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
我从来没有。
I NEVER HAVE.
我很抱歉。
I'M SORRY.
哇！他心跳变慢了。
WHOA! HE'S BRADYING DOWN.
胸管里涌出大量血液。
CHEST TUBE IS
POURING OUT BLOOD.
走吧。
LET'S GO.
输两单位O型阴性血，然后叫手术室。
GET TWO UNITS OF O-NEG IN
AND CALL THE O.R.
你让我失去了一个手术。
YOU COST ME A PROCEDURE.
我该问怎么了？
AM I SUPPOSED
TO ASK HOW?
你本该替我看着那只无脉的脚。
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BABY-SIT
THAT PULSELESS FOOT FOR ME.
格林让放射科医生对他下手了。
GREENE LET
THE RADIOLOGISTS AT HIM.
我没想到那是我的职责范围。
I DIDN'T REALIZE
THAT WAS PART OF
MY JOB DESCRIPTION.
嗯。嗯，你还在学习。
HMM. WELL,
YOU'RE STILL LEARNING.
嗯哼。
MM-HMM.
你第一天怎么样？
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY?
如预期。
AS EXPECTED.
你不是受虐狂
YOU ARE EITHER A MASOCHIST
就是我见过最固执的女人
OR THE STUBBORNEST WOMAN
I'VE EVER MET
但我不得不说我佩服你的毅力。
BUT I HAVE TO SAY
I ADMIRE YOUR FORTITUDE.
我受不了戴尔那样的家伙发号施令。
I COULDN'T HANDLE TAKING ORDERS
FROM A WEASEL LIKE DALE.
这是恭维吗？
IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO BE A COMPLIMENT?
听起来像是。
SOUNDED LIKE ONE TO ME.
哦，你可以穿长外套。
OH, AND YOU CAN WEAR
THE LONG COAT.
你穿着更好看。
IT LOOKS BETTER ON YOU.
海瑟薇：胸管引出700毫升。
Hathaway:
700cc's OUT THE CHEST TUBE.
把他送上去，卡特。
TAKE HIM UP, CARTER.
他们知道他需要开胸手术吗？
THEY KNOW HE NEEDS
A THORACOTOMY?
是的。三号手术室。
YEAH. O.R. THREE.
让血库送四单位特定血型。
HAVE THE BLOOD BANK SEND UP
FOUR UNITS TYPE SPECIFIC.
是的。我们没有为重大创伤做好准备。
YUP. WE WERE NOT PREPARED
FOR A MAJOR TRAUMA.
他昏倒的时候你应该打电话的。
YOU SHOULD HAVE CALLED
WHEN HE CRUMPED.
我们忙着保护他的气道。
WE WERE A LITTLE BUSY
PROTECTING HIS AIRWAY.
暂停。
TIME OUT.
你们应该打电话的。
YOU GUYS SHOULD
HAVE CALLED.
没办法…
THERE WAS NO WAY...
啊…你们应该打电话的
AH... YOU GUYS
SHOULD HAVE CALLED
我们必须为任何事情做好准备。
AND WE HAVE TO BE
PREPARED FOR ANYTHING.
我本来会做好准备的…
I WOULD HAVE
BEEN PREPARED...
没有人该受责备。
NOBODY'S TO BLAME.
我们治疗了病人。
WE TREATED THE PATIENT.
我们继续吧。
LET'S MOVE ON.
你想留下来回顾一下运行录像吗？
YOU WANT TO STICK AROUND
AND REVIEW THE RUN TAPE?
不。不。
NO.
狗狗。是的。
DOGGY. YEAH.
你想摸摸狗狗吗？
YOU WANT TO PET THE DOGGY?
嗯。
MMM.
哦，那很好。
OH, THAT IS GOOD.
你希望他以某种方式回应，你知道吗？
YOU WANT HIM TO RESPOND
IN SOME WAY, YOU KNOW?
指点或发出某种声音。
TO POINT OR TO MAKE
SOME KIND OF SOUND.
（模仿风声）
( imitating wind )
（猫叫声）
( meowing )
小猫说，“喵。
KITTY SAYS, "MEOW.
喵。”
MEOW."
你想摸摸小猫吗？
DO YOU WANT TO PET THE KITTY?
（呜咽）
( whines )
哦。
OH.
不喜欢小猫吗？
DON'T LIKE THE KITTY?
没关系。
THAT'S OKAY.
一个快速的拥抱，然后回去工作。
ONE QUICK HUG,
THEN BACK TO WORK.
什么？
WHAT?
他得学会专注。
HE'S GOT TO LEARN TO FOCUS.
哦，来吧，给他个机会。
OH, COME ON,
GIVE HIM A BREAK.
他才一岁。
HE'S ONLY A YEAR OLD.
你不能给他放假。
YOU CAN'T GIVE HIM A BREAK.
他不像其他一岁的孩子。
HE'S NOT LIKE
OTHER ONE-YEAR-OLDS.
他需要持续的语言刺激。
HE NEEDS CONSTANT
VERBAL STIMULI.
（咆哮）
( growls )
嘿，你试试。
HEY, YOU TRY.
好吧，伙计。
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
嗯…我们开始吧。
UM... HERE WE GO.
狗狗。狗狗。
DOGGY. DOGGY.
汪。
ARF.
嘿，狗狗。汪。
HEY, DOGGY. ARF.
汪，汪，汪。
ARF, ARF, ARF.
汪，瑞茜。汪。
ARF, REESE. ARF.
我做不到。
I CAN'T DO THIS.
你必须学会。
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO LEARN.
每周来两次是没用的。
COMING HERE TWICE A WEEK
ISN'T GOING TO DO IT.
听着，我今天下午也许能把那孩子留在这里
LISTEN, I MIGHT
HAVE BEEN ABLE
但他明天会出去做同样的事情。
TO KEEP THAT KID HERE
THIS AFTERNOON
呃，他妈妈在椅子上。
BUT HE WOULD HAVE GONE
OUT AND DONE THE
SAME THING TOMORROW.
你想让我去和她谈谈吗？
UH, HIS MOM'S IN CHAIRS.
不，不。我来。
YOU WANT ME TO GO
TALK TO HER?
忘了号码？
NO, NO. I'LL DO IT.
呃，没有。
FORGET A NUMBER?
你还在？
UH, NO.
是的，我被耽搁了。
YOU STILL HERE?
嘿，你需要一些帮助。
YEAH, I GOT SIDETRACKED.
好的，接手皮疹病例。
HEY, YOU COULD USE SOME HELP.
我正在考虑更长久的事情。
OKAY, TAKE RASHES.
呃，过敏？
I WAS THINKING
OF SOMETHING MORE PERMANENT.
实际上，我是说成为你的全职助理。
UH, ALLERGIES?
是的。
ACTUALLY, I MEANT BEING
YOUR FULL-TIME P.A.
我一直在考虑。
YEAH. I BEEN
THINKING ABOUT IT.
我很想只和孩子们一起工作一段时间。
I'D LOVE TO JUST WORK
WITH KIDS FOR A WHILE.
我很擅长，而且，不知何故，这似乎更有意义。
I'M GOOD AT IT AND, SOMEHOW,
IT SEEMS MORE WORTHWHILE.
嗯，我不知道。
WELL, I DON'T
KNOW ABOUT THAT.
嗯，至少你知道你站在哪一边。
WELL, AT LEAST YOU KNOW
WHOSE SIDE YOU'RE ON.
你知道，我…我很想。
YOU KNOW, I'D...
I'D LOVE TO.
我只是觉得我把所有筹码都用在安斯普上面了。
I JUST THINK I'VE USED UP
ALL MY CHIPS WITH ANSPAUGH.
我有点影响力。
I'VE GOT SOME PULL.
我想我能解决。
I THINK I COULD
WORK IT OUT.
太好了。我很喜欢。
GREAT. I'D LOVE THAT.
太棒了。
EXCELLENT.
好的。
GOOD.
（清嗓子）
( clears throat )
是啊，嗨。
YEAH, HI.
请问能给我UNOS的移植协调员吗？
MAY I HAVE THE TRANSPLANT
COORDINATOR FOR UNOS, PLEASE?
好的。
OKAY.
我给你打了两次传呼。
I PAGED YOU TWICE.
我不想现在谈论它。
I DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT YET.
那太糟糕了，因为我觉得我应该得到一个解释。
THAT'S TOO BAD, 'CAUSE I THINK
I DESERVE AN EXPLANATION.
如果你想让我感觉糟糕，我确实感觉糟糕。
IF YOU WANT ME
TO FEEL BAD, I DO.
我对自己非常失望。
I'M REALLY DISAPPOINTED
IN MYSELF.
你应该这样
YOU SHOULD BE
那不是解释。
AND THAT'S NOT
AN EXPLANATION.
我不知道它是怎么开始的。
I DON'T KNOW
HOW IT STARTED.
我…你认为我能做到。
I... YOU THOUGHT
I COULD DO IT.
我想给你留下深刻印象
I WANTED TO IMPRESS YOU
然后失控了。
AND IT SPUN
OUT OF CONTROL.
我很抱歉。
I'M SORRY.
你认为你能完成什么？
WHAT DID YOU THINK YOU
WERE GOING TO ACCOMPLISH?
我不知道。
I DON'T KNOW.
我以为我可以自学。
I THOUGHT I COULD
LEARN ON MY OWN.
哦，太棒了。你可以自学。
OH, GREAT. YOU CAN
LEARN ON YOUR OWN.
那你就不需要在这里了。
WELL, YOU DON'T NEED
TO BE HERE THEN.
你让病人处于危险之中，露西。
YOU ENDANGERED PATIENTS, LUCY.
你不需要
YOU DON'T NEED
让我感觉糟糕——我感觉糟透了。
TO MAKE ME FEEL BAD--
I FEEL HORRIBLE.
嗯，如果这是关于你的话，那会奏效
WELL, THAT WOULD WORK
IF THIS WAS ABOUT YOU
但第一条规则
BUT RULE NUMBER ONE
那里是永远不要以你为中心。
DOWN THERE IS
IT'S NEVER ABOUT YOU.
你知道吗，回家吧。
YOU KNOW, GO HOME.
除非你认真学习，否则别回来。
DON'T COME BACK
UNLESS YOU'RE SERIOUS
ABOUT LEARNING SOMETHING.
如果你再对我撒谎
AND IF YOU EVER
LIE TO ME AGAIN
你可以找另一个轮岗。
YOU CAN LOOK
FOR ANOTHER ROTATION.
你回来干什么？
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING BACK HERE?
我在等烤架加热。
I'M WAITING FOR THE GRILL
TO HEAT UP.
我以为今天是自给自足的夜晚。
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
FEND-FOR-YOURSELF NIGHT.
嗯，我厌倦了自给自足。
WELL, I'M SICK
OF FEND-FOR-YOURSELF.
我给我们买了牛排。
I GOT US SOME STEAKS.
牛排听起来不错。
STEAKS SOUND GOOD.
你还有一份给我吗？
YOU GOT ANOTHER ONE
OF THOSE FOR ME?
是的。
YUP.
袋子里是什么？
WHAT'S IN THE BAG?
是一个，呃…怀孕测试。
IT'S A, UH...
PREGNANCY TEST.
为了确定。
TO BE SURE.
没必要。我来月经了。
NO NEED.
I STARTED MY PERIOD.
嗯，我想我浪费了17.5美元。
WELL, I GUESS
I WASTED $17.50.
嗯，留着下次用。
WELL, SAVE IT
FOR NEXT TIME.
我开玩笑的。
I'M KIDDING.
那是个玩笑。
THAT WAS A JOKE.
我们躲过了一劫，不是吗？
WE DODGED THE BULLET
THERE, DIDN'T WE?
是的。
YUP.
那很好，对吧？
THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
是的，是的。
YEAH, YEAH.
不过，一整天，我都在想，“哇，一个孩子。”
THOUGH, ALL DAY, I KEPT
THINKING, "WOW, A KID."
你知道，那真的会…
YOU KNOW, THAT WOULD REALLY...
改变我的生活。
CHANGE MY LIFE.
我们的生活。
OUR LIFE.
它会改变我们的。
IT WOULD CHANGE OURS.
好的，我们的生活。
OKAY, OUR LIVES.
那会很糟糕，对吧？
THAT WOULD BE BAD, RIGHT?
你知道吗？
YOU KNOW WHAT?
我改变主意了。
I CHANGED MY MIND.
我不想开玩笑。
I DON'T WANT TO JOKE ABOUT IT.
是的。
YEAH.
也许我不是在开玩笑。
MAYBE I'M NOT JOKING.